Guide to the Larry LaRocco Collection 1982-1994
Boise State University Library, Special Collections and Archives
- Maps, 12
  - Set XXI - Topographical Maps
    - Satellite photograph of Idaho State, undated
    - Palouse ranger district, Clearwater National Forest
    - Idaho Panhandle National Forests, St. Marie's ranger district, 1994
    - St. Joe's National Forest, 1966
    - St. Joe's Forest demonstration project, 1994
    - Montana - Idaho split, undated
    - Boise National Forest, 1989
    - Rapid River, Payette, 1987
    - Payette National Forest, 1983
    - Clearwater National Forest, 1980
    - Sandpoint ranger district, undated
    - Warm Lake, 1987
    - Priest Lake Bonners Ferry Ranch district, undated
    - Clearwater, undated
  - Set XXII - McClure/Andrus Proposal (Topographical Maps)
    - Targhee National Forest, proposed wilderness areas, visitors map, 1987
    - Targhee National Forest, proposed wilderness areas, visitors map, 1987
    - Sawtooth wilderness, undated
    - Sawtooth National Forest, 1970
    - Sawtooth National Forest, Fairfield and Ketchum districts, 1985
    - Salmon National Forest, proposed wilderness areas, 1987
    - Payette National Forest, proposed wilderness areas, 1983
    - Kaniksu National Forest, Priest Lake and Bonners Ferry ranger districts proposed wilderness areas, 1987
    - Sandpoint ranger district proposed wilderness areas
    - Clearwater National Forest, Canyon, Palouse and Perce ranger districts, 1980
    - Selway - Bitterroot, proposed wilderness, 1987
    - Challis National Forest, west half, 1984
    - Challis National Forest, east half, 1984
    - Caribou National Forest, 1973
    - Warm Lake Area, 1987
    - Boise National Forest, 1977
  - Set XXIII - Maps of Motorized Trails HR 3732
    - Payette National Forest, travel map, 1994
    - Payette National Forest, west half - topographical
    - Payette National Forest, topographical, 1992
    - Kaniksu National Forest, House Bill #3732, trails open to off highway vehicle use, 1988
    - St. Joe's National Forest, undated
    - Nez Perce National Forest, forest boundary, wilderness boundary, open trail systems, 1981
    - Coeur d'Alene National Forest, House Bill #3732 - trials open to off highway vehicle use, 1989
    - Boise National Forest, visitors map, topographical, 1984
    - Clearwater National Forest, topographical, 1986
  - Set XXIV - Maps of Idaho
    Idaho Department of Transportation 1: 100,000 moved To BSU Albertsons Library Map Department
    - Arco, ID, 1989-p; Map 1
    - Bighorn Crags, ID-MT, 1990-t; Map 2
    - Blackfoot, ID, 1984-t; Map 3
    - Boise, ID, 1990-t; Map 4
    - Bonners Ferry, ID-MT, 1989-t; Map 5
    - Borah Peak, ID-MT, 1988-p; Map 6
    - Challis, ID, 1989-t; Map 7
    - Circular Butte, ID, 1985-t; Map 8
    - Coeur d'Alene, ID-MT, 1989-t; Map 9
    - Craters of the moon, ID, 1984-t; Map 10
    - Deadwood River, ID, 1990-t; Map 11
    - Dubois, ID-MT, 1986-t; Map 12
    - Elk City, ID, 1989-t; Map 13
    - Fairfield, ID, 1989-t; Map 14
    - Glenns Ferry, ID, 1988-t; Map 15
    - Grangeville, ID-MT-WA, 1984-t; Map 16
    - Hamilton, MT-ID, 1990-t; Map 17
    - Headquarters, ID-MT, 1984-t; Map 18
    - Idaho City, ID, 1990-t; Map 19
    - Kooskia, ID, 1990-t; Map 20
    - Lake Walcott, ID, 1989-p; Map 21
    - Leadore, ID-MT, 1989-t; Map 22
    - Malad City, ID-UT, 1985-t; Map 23
  - Set XXIV - Maps of Idaho
    Idaho department of Transportation 1: 100,000 moved to BSU Albertsons Library Map Department
    - McCall, ID-OR, 1988-t; Map 24
    - Missoula West, MT-ID, 1990-t; Map 25
    - Mountain Home, ID, 1988-p; Map 26
    - Murphy, ID, 1988-t; Map 27
    - Nez Perce Pass, ID-MT, 1989-t; Map 28
    - Oakley, ID, 1989-p; Map 29
    - Orofino, ID-WA, 1984-t; Map 30
    - Palisades, ID-WY, 1989-t; Map 31
    - Pistol Creek, ID, 1989-t; Map 32
    - Pocatello, ID, 1985-t; Map 33
    - Potlach, ID, 1990-t; Map 34
    - Preston, ID-WY-UT, 1986-t; Map 35
    - Rexburg, ID-WY, 1989-p; Map 36
    - Riggins, ID-OR, 1989-t; Map 37
    - St. Maries, ID, 1989-t; Map 38
    - Salmon, ID-MT, 1985-t; Map 39
    - Sandpoint, ID-MT, 1990-t; Map 40
    - Sheep Creek, ID, 1986-t; Map 41
    - Soda Springs, ID-WY, 1985-t; Map 42
    - Sun Valley, ID, 1990-t; Map 43
    - Triangle, ID, 1990-t; Map 44
    - Twin Falls, ID, 1990-t; Map 45
    - Wallace, ID-MT, 1989-p; Map 46
  - Set XXIV - Maps of Idaho
    - Warren, ID, 1989-t; Map 47
    - Weiser, ID-OR, 1990-t; Map 48
    - White Cloud Peaks, ID, 1989-t; Map 49
- Photograph and snapshots, 13
  The photographs contained in the Larry LaRocco Collection consist of over 200 photographs and negatives. Many are candid snapshots taken during personal appearances. A large portion of photographs directly relate to his three campaigns for Congress. LaRocco was frequently photographed with constituents in visited Washington, DC and on his visits home to Idaho. Samples of these photos are in the collection.
  Several dignitaries were photographed with the Representative, such as Senator Albert Gore, Jr., Governor Cecil Andrus and Speaker of the House, Tom Foley. Formal portraits of LaRocco in color and black and white can be found the files. Representative LaRocco and Senator Gephart were photographed touring Boise computer company, Micron, Inc.
  Photographs relating to legislation have been included in the series. Visits to the Birds of Prey Natural Conservation Area, the North Fork of the Payette River, and a Pro-Choice Rally at the State Capitol show LaRocco's interest in controversial Idaho issues. Representative LaRocco proposed to honor the participants in the Persian Gulf War, a medal, photographs of which can be found in the collection. The actual medal can be seen in the collection's memorabilia. Photographs of Automatic Weapons restricted by the "Brady Bill", defense photos of the Stealth Bomber and the Super Conducting Super Collider are included in the collection.
  - Awards (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Awards
  - Campaign (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Cam
  - Campaign (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Campaign (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constituents: Idaho (Box 1, Folder 5)
    ConID
  - Constituents: Washington, DC (Box 1, Folder 6)
    ConWDC
  - Dignitaries: Albert Gore (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Dig AG
  - Dignitaries: Bethine Church (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Dig BC
  - Dignitaries: Idaho (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Dig ID
  - Dignitaries: Tom Foley (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Dig TF
  - Family (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Fam
  - Idaho Public Relations: Frank Church Conference on Public Affair (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Ipr-Fc
  - Idaho Public Relations: General (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Danny Thompson Memorial Golf Tournament Weiser, Idaho
  - Idaho Public Relations: Micron, Corporation (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Micron, Corporation; IdPR-Mic; Appleton, Steve; Gephart, Richard
  - Idaho Public Relations: Persian Gulf Medal Presentation (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Persian Gulf Veterans National Medal Act IdPR-PGM
  - Idaho Public Relations: Veterans Day Speech (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Veterans Affairs; IPR Vet
  - Issues: Automatic Weapons (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Gun Control Automatic Weapons IsAW
  - Issues: Birds of Prey (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Snake River Birds of Prey Natural Area IsBP
  - Issues: Drawdowns (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Columbia River Salmon IsDRA
  - Issues: Grazing (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Grazing Public Lands IsGRA
  - Issues: Lottery (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Idaho-Lotteries IsLOT
  - Issues: North Fork of The Payette (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Payette River Hydroelectric Power IsPAY
  - Issues: Persian Gulf War Medal (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Persian Gulf War IsPGM
  - Issues: Pro Choice Rally (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Women's Rights; Abortion; Idaho-Demonstrators; Rosalie Sorrels; Karl Brooks; Cecil Andrus; IsPC
  - Issues: Salmon River (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Wilderness Areas Salmon River IsSALR
  - Issues: Stealth Bomber (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Stealth Bomber IsSB
  - Issues: Super Conducting Super Collider (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Super Conducting Super Collider IsSCSC
  - Issues: Wilderness Town Meeting (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Wilderness Areas IsWILD
  - Issues: Wolves (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Wolves IsWOL
  - Office: Washington DC (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Ofwdc
  - Portraits (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Por
  - Portraits, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Por70
  - Portraits: Before Microphone (Box 1, Folder 33)
    PorM.
  - Portraits: Outdoors (Box 1, Folder 34)
    PorOut
  - Youth Groups (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Additions, 14
  - Wilderness
    - Agriculture Subcommitte H/Discharge, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Wilderness Legislation
    - Archeology, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Wilderness Legislation; Historic Preservation; Wilderness Areas-Mallard-Larkin; Cultural Property, Protection of
    - H.R. 3732, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Wilderness Areas; Water Rights; Forest and Forestry
    - Bureau of Land Management Wilderness, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Wilderness Areas; Public Lands
    - Boise Hearings, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Wilderness Legislation; Roadless Areas; Boulder-White Clouds; Forest and Forestry
    - Boundary County, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Wilderness Legislation; Timber Sales; Wilderness Areas; Roadless Areas; Coeur d'Alene; Land Use; Litigation
    - Boundary County, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Wilderness Legislation; Litigation
    - Boundary Trails, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Trails
    - Centennial Trail, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Central Idaho Wilderness Act, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Wilderness Legislation; Roadless Areas; Land Use; Meadow Creek
    - Chronology, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Clearwater Agreement, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Wilderness Legislation; Wilderness Areas; Litigation
    - Clearwater National Forest, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Colorado Wilderness, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      S.1029; H.R.195; H.R.631
    - Contacts, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Wilderness Areas; Witnesses
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Wilderness Legislation; Wilderness Areas; Timber Sales; Forest and Forestry
    - Delegation Effort, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Wilderness Legislation; Roadless Areas; Timber; Water Rights; Private Property
    - Ecosystem Study, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Ecosystem Management
    - Enviros List, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Wilderness Areas; Timber Sales
    - Wilderness Equity Act, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Fish Lake, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - French Creek, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Grandmother Mountain, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Gospel Hump, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Wilderness Areas; Roads
    - Grazing, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Great Bum, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Hearings: Idaho Wilderness, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Wilderness Areas; Public Lands; Forest and Forestry; Meadow Creek; Wilderness Legislation
    - Wilson/Jackson Bar Airstrip, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Wilderness Areas--Airports
    - January 15th Meeting, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      Wilderness Areas; Wilderness Legislation; Timber; Forest Management
    - Governor's Timber Task Force, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Wilderness Areas; Timber
    - Jemez National Recreation Area, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Recreation Areas
      H.R.2502
    - Jobs, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Job Task Force, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Kostmayer Amendment, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Lewiston Hearing, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      Wilderness Areas; Wilderness Legislation
    - Lime Creek, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Long Canyon/Selkirk Crest, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Maps, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Marble Creek, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      Historic Preservation
    - Marlenee Amendment, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Montana Wilderness Areas
    - Meadow Creek, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      Wilderness Areas; Ecology
    - Mining Minerals, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      Mine and Mineral Resources; Public Lands
    - Montana Senate Bill, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      S.1696
    - Montana Adjacent Areas, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      Wilderness Areas; Recreation Areas
    - Montana Wilderness Hearing, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      Wilderness Legislation; Lumber; Petroleum; All Terrain Vehicles
      H.R.2473
    - Montana Wilderness, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Negotiations, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      Wilderness Areas; Clearwater Forest; Meadow Creek
    - Nevada Wilderness, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Northern Rockies Ecosystem Protection Act, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Hearings
    - Off-Road Vehicles, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Other Wilderness Bills Enacted, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Outfitters, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Frank Church River of No Return; Outfitters and Guides
    - Outfitters, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Policy Analysis Group Report, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Peace Rock/Breadwinner, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Position Paper, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Timber; Biotic Community; Ecosystem Management; Water Rights
    - Prescriptions, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Recent Wilderness Press, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Wilderness Areas; Clippings (Newspapers, Books, Etc.)
    - Press, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Press, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Press, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Private Property, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Wilderness Areas; Land Tenure
    - Rapid River, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Wilderness Areas; Rivers
    - Release, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Water Rights
    - Roadless Area, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - RS 2477, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Wilderness Areas; Roads; Trails
    - Scientific Assessment, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Soil Conservation Service Needs - Weather, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Watershed Management
    - Selway-Bitterroot Adds, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Wilderness Areas; Boundaries
    - Special Management Areas Prescriptions, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Snow Peak/Buck Creek, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Statements--Larry LaRocco, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - St. Joe, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Study, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Timber Demonstration Project, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Timber Facts, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Wilderness Tourism, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      Outdoor Recreation
    - Town Meetings, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - University of Idaho Wilderness Forum, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Utah Wilderness Act 1984, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      Utah Wilderness Areas
    - Vanderbilt, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Idaho Wilderness Areas, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Idaho Wilderness Areas, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Special Management Areas, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Economic Statistics Idaho National Forest, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      Wilderness Areas; Forest and Forestry
    - Wilderness Economics, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      Wilderness Areas; Ecosystem Management
    - Anti-Wilderness Correspondence, 19931992 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Compromise, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Meadow Creek, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Wilderness Areas; Correspondence
    - Pro-Northern Rockies Ecosystem Protection Act, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Pro-Wilderness Groups, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Pro-Wilderness Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Panhandle National Forest, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Clearwater National Forest, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Nez Perce National Forest, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Payette National Forest, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Boise National Forest, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Wilderness Issues, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Wilderness Legislation; Historical Sites
    - General Areas, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Watershed Analysis, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Water Language, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Water Language, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Wilderness Legislation; Water Rights
    - Watershed Projects--Idaho Forests, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Wilderness Areas; Rivers--Salmon
    - Wilderness Act, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Williams Substitute Amendment, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Wilderness Values, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Wilderness Management, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Wind River Pack Bridge, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Joe Zimmer, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Headwaters, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Wilderness Areas; Wilderness Legislation; Water Rights
    - Memos, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Legislative Agenda, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Timber Industry; Livestock; Grazing; Bombing Range
    - Clinton Administration, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Confidential Memo, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Internal Memos on Wilderness, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      Water Rights; Land Tenure; Wilderness Areas; Meadow Creek; Salmon; Grazing; Forest and Forestry
    - Off-Road Vehicle Trails, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      Wilderness Areas; Trails; All Terrain Vehicles
    - Memos to Larry LaRocco, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      Wilderness Legislation; Timber; Forest and Forestry
    - Release Language, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      Wilderness Legislation; Timber
    - Release Language, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Wilderness Water Language, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Constituent Letters, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      Wilderness Areas; Wilderness Legislation; Forest and Forestry; Timber; Salmon; Rivers--Columbia, Snake; Wolves; Caribou; Wetlands; Forest Management; Hydroelectric Power Plant; Grizzly Bear; Spotted Owl; Water Rights; Wetlands
    - Forest Service H.R. 1570, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      Wilderness Legislation; Wilderness Areas; Wildlife
    - Forest Service H.R. 1570, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Iran; Iraq; Syria; Libya; Nuclear Weapons; International Relation; Economic Reform; International Development
    - Bonneville Power Administration, 1985-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Maps; Bonneville Project Act; Power; Environment; Dams; Hydropower; Salmon; Wildlife; Endangered Species; Rivers; Conservation; Recreation
    - Briefing Book on the Former Soviet Union, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      International Relations; Maps; International Development; Economic Growth; Human Rights; Environment; Military; Armenia; Azerbaijan; Belarus; Georgia; Kazakhstan; Kyrgyzstan; Moldova; Russia; Tajikistan; Turkmenistan
    - Environmental and Energy Study Conference, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Environment; Power; Acid Rain; Wilderness; Asbestos; Air Quality; Coal; Water Quality; Endangered Species; Budgets; Natural Gas; Nuclear Waste; Nuclear Weapons; Minerals; Pesticides; Conservation; Hazardous Wastes; Superfund Sit
    - Health Security Plan, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Health Planning; Health Service Administration; AIDS; Insurance Reform; Medicaid; Medicare; Mental Health
    - Medicare and Medicaid Programs, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Health Care Administration
    - Morrison Knusden: Rail Transit Programs, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Railroads; Transportation
    - The Securities Industry Briefing Book: Role of the US Capital Ma, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Taxation; International Trade; International Development; Economic Growth
    - US Relations with Developing Countries, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      International Development; International Trade; International Relations; International Finance; International Relations -- Environmental Aspects; AIDS; Population Growth
- Memorabilia
  - Campaign Banner
  - Thank You Poster from Girl Scout Troops 792 164 of Idaho City
  - Poster from Jessica
  - Potlatch Samples of Wood: Western White Pine and Grand Fir
  - LaRocco Campaign Stickers
  - Photograph: Odyssey of the Mind Team.
  - Model of Northrop B-2: U.S. Air Force (stand and plane)
  - Inaugural Production Paperweight
  - Congressman LaRocco Bronze Medallion Persian Gulf War, 1993
  - David Taylor Research Center Book
  - Guest Book, Washington, DC Office
  - Guest Book, Washington, DC Office
  - Guest Book, Washington, DC Office
  - Guest and Speaker Badges
  - LaRocco Certificate of Appreciation: Kiwanis Club, Emmett Id., 1990
  - World Cup Soccer Pin, 1992
  - World Cup Soccer Pin, 1994
  - World Cup Soccer Pin
  - LaRocco Keychain
  - Senior Citizen Hall of Fame Award, 1992
  - Guest Speaker Certificate, 1992
  - Certificate of Appreciation: Southwest Idaho Private Industry Council, 1983-1994
  - Resolution of Recognition: Idaho Credit Union League, 1994
  - Certificate of Appreciation: ApHC, 1993
  - Hubble Space Telescope Poster, 1993